stockwatch.com 2017-11-17

# Stockwatch

This Privacy Policy is applicable to all _Stockwatch Products & Services_ which include, without limitation, the Stockwatch website(s) at stockwatch.com; the software applications offered on the Stockwatch website(s) including the Live Ticker, the Day-Trader Workstation, and the Stockwatch Desktop; the mobile software applications (“apps”) offered through the Stockwatch website(s) or through various third-party websites or third-party mobile applications, including apps for Apple iPhone®, Apple iPad®, Google Android™ , and Blackberry®; the Daily Stockwatch online publication; Stockwatch corporate and advertising services including Stockwatch Articles Email List, XML Feed; and all other Stockwatch products and services offered now and in the future.

_If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy with respect to Stockwatch Products & Services, please send an email to [webmaster@stockwatch.com](mailto:webmaster@stockwatch.com) or call us at 1-800-268-6397 (1-604-687-1500)._

## 1\. Stockwatch Products & Services

This section describes the Stockwatch Privacy Policy as it relates specifically to Stockwatch-provided products and services and any information collected and used by Stockwatch directly or indirectly through those products and services. This section specifically excludes all policies relating to Third-Party Services used by or embedded within Stockwatch Products & Services.

### Personal Information Collected

In order to provide Stockwatch Products & Services, we may ask you for certain Personal Information including, without limitation, your name, postal address, telephone number, email address, payment card number, payment card expiry date, payment card security code, and other such information. 

If you are a securities industry professional we may also ask you for certain Personal Information related to your employment including, without limitation, your employer’s name, employer’s address, your job title or job function, and other such information.

### Personal Information Usage

The Personal Information that you provide to Stockwatch is used directly or indirectly for the provision of your selected Stockwatch Products & Services. Such usage may include customer support, technical support, usage reporting, account management, payment processing, administration, audit and control, customer communications, and other purposes that are compatible with the provision of Stockwatch Products & Services.

### Personal Information Protection

Stockwatch secures your Personal Information using commercially reasonable methods that are consistent with generally accepted industry practices, and that provide no less security than is applied to the systems and data assets belonging to Stockwatch.

In particular, Personal Information is entered only through SSL encrypted (HTTPS) web pages and stored on computer systems that are located in Canada and that are both owned by and controlled by Stockwatch.

### Personal Information Disclosure

Stockwatch does not share or sell Personal Information and will not disclose your Personal Information to any third-party except as described in this Privacy Policy and, in general, where you would reasonably expect Stockwatch to disclose Personal Information in order to provide your Products & Services.

Stockwatch will disclose your Personal Information:

  * To our trusted Payment Processor, credit card companies, and/or banks, as required, for payment processing purposes.
  * To our trusted Stock Market Data Providers and other Third-Party Data Providers, and their authorized agents, when required to fulfill the contractual end-user reporting obligations of Stockwatch, and/or your contractual obligations with respect to optional real-time data services, with or without individual “click-on” or signed Data Agreements.
  * To our trusted online publishing contractors in support of “Daily Stockwatch” publication and subscription services.
  * To our trusted contractors and agents when required to fulfill their purposes.
  * To legal authorities when compelled to do so by court order, or if Stockwatch suspects, at its sole discretion, the possibility of fraudulent and/or criminal activity involving a customer or customer account.
  * To government authorities when required to do so for administration, taxation, regulatory, audit or other such purposes.

When Personal Information must be disclosed, Stockwatch endeavors to provide the minimum amount of Personal Information required to fulfil the purpose.

### Website “Cookies”

In website terminology, “cookies” are small data files stored on your device by your web browser at the request of various websites that you visit. Cookies are typically used to store information about your current website session, your website preferences and/or your website usage. Like many websites, Stockwatch uses cookies to manage authenticated website sessions and to store certain website viewing preferences, but does not use them to store any personally identifiable information. Stockwatch uses cookies and other website technologies in a manner consistent with generally accepted industry practices.

## 2\. Third-Party Services

Like many commercial websites and online service providers, Stockwatch may use various well-known Third-Party Analytics and Advertising Services. This section provides links to the individual privacy policies and other relevant terms of these Third-Party Services which operate independently of Stockwatch and are specifically excluded from the privacy policies that relate to Stockwatch-provided products and services.

### Analytics Services

Stockwatch Products & Services may use one or more Third-Party Analytics Services to gather usage information. Such information is gathered directly by the Third-Party Analytics Services through embedded links in Stockwatch Products & Services. Stockwatch does not see the raw data collected in this way, and only has access to such data in an aggregated and anonymous form. The information collected by these Third-Party Analytics Services is subject to their individual privacy policies, and other applicable policies and terms, as follows:

  * Google Analytics: 
    * Google Analytics Terms of Service ([www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html](http://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html))
    * Google “Partners Usage Policy” ([www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners))
    * Google Privacy Policy ([www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html))

Stockwatch uses these Third-Party Analytics Services in a manner that is consistent with generally accepted industry practices.

### Advertising Services

Stockwatch Products & Services may use one or more Third-Party Advertising Services to provide Display Advertising. Stockwatch is not responsible for the appearance or content of such Display Advertising, for any links associated with such Display Advertising, or for any web pages, websites or web-based services linked-to from such Display Advertising. Stockwatch is not responsible for the privacy or usage of any personal or other information that you explicitly or implicitly provide to Third-Party Advertising Services through their Display Advertising including, without limitation, information gathered when Display Advertising is viewed or “clicked-on”, information entered on web forms associated with Display Advertising, information entered or gathered automatically on external web pages, websites or web services that you navigate to from Display Advertising, or information stored and/or tracked in website cookies by the Third-Party Advertising Services. The information collected by these Third-Party Advertising Services is subject to their individual privacy policies, and other applicable policies and terms, as follows:

  * Google AdWords and related Google services: 
    * Google Advertising Program Terms ([www.google.com/intl/en_ca/adwords/select/TCUSA2013-01.html](http://www.google.com/intl/en_ca/adwords/select/TCUSA2013-01.html))
    * Google AdWords Policies ([www.google.com/ads/policies](http://www.google.com/ads/policies))
    * Google Advertising Cookies Policy ([www.google.com/ads/cookies](http://www.google.com/ads/cookies))
    * Google “Partners Usage Policy” ([www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners))
    * Google Privacy Policy ([www.google.com/privacy.html](http://www.google.com/privacy.html))

Stockwatch uses these Third-Party Advertising Services in a manner that is consistent with generally accepted industry practices.

## 3\. Implied Consent

For the convenience of our users and customers, and for practical reasons, Stockwatch relies primarily on your implied consent for the collection and use of Personal Information and other information provided by its customers and users, or gathered automatically through usage.

By using Stockwatch Products & Services YOU CONSENT to:

  * The collection, retention, usage and disclosure of your Personal Information by Stockwatch for purposes compatible with providing your services and according to this Privacy Policy.
  * The use of website “cookies” by Stockwatch according to this Privacy Policy.
  * The collection, retention, usage and disclosure by Third-Party Analytics Services of your usage information, and the disclosure of aggregated and anonymous usage data to Stockwatch, according to the privacy policies, and other applicable policies and terms, of the Third-Party Analytics Providers.
  * The collection, retention, usage and disclosure by Third-Party Advertising Services of your Display Advertising viewing and clicking usage, and any personal or other information that you explicitly provide through such Display Advertising, according to the privacy policies, and other applicable policies and terms, of the Third-Party Advertising Providers.

DO NOT use Stockwatch Products & Services unless you agree with and consent to this Privacy Policy, and the applicable privacy policies of the Third-Party Services used by Stockwatch.

## 4\. Changes, Errors & Omissions

Privacy on the Internet is a constantly evolving area, as are the Stockwatch Products & Services and the Third-Party Services used by Stockwatch. No privacy policy can cover all possible situations at all times.

The Stockwatch Privacy Policy will be updated from time-to-time and is subject to change without notice. While Stockwatch has tried to make this Privacy Policy complete in all important respects, Stockwatch is not responsible for changes, errors or omissions.

Regardless of any changes, errors or omissions to this Privacy Policy, the approach Stockwatch takes to privacy will be respectful of our customers, will be consistent with generally accepted industry practices, and will be compliant with legal requirements.

Copyright © 2017, Canjex Publishing Ltd. All rights reserved. “Stockwatch” is a registered trademark of Canjex Publishing Ltd.
